[
{"id":92,"name":"Gastly","speed":80,"special_defense":35,"special_attack":100,"defense":30,"attack":35,"hp":30,"types":["poison","ghost"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/092.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/092.gif"},
{"id":7,"name":"Squirtle","speed":43,"special_defense":64,"special_attack":50,"defense":65,"attack":48,"hp":44,"types":["water"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/007.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/007.gif"},
{"id":74,"name":"Geodude","speed":20,"special_defense":30,"special_attack":30,"defense":100,"attack":80,"hp":40,"types":["ground","rock"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/074.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/074.gif"},
{"id":39,"name":"Jigglypuff","speed":20,"special_defense":25,"special_attack":45,"defense":20,"attack":45,"hp":115,"types":["fairy","normal"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/039.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/039.gif"},
{"id":56,"name":"Mankey","speed":70,"special_defense":45,"special_attack":35,"defense":35,"attack":80,"hp":40,"types":["fighting"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/056.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/056.gif"},
{"id":23,"name":"Ekans","speed":55,"special_defense":54,"special_attack":40,"defense":44,"attack":60,"hp":35,"types":["poison"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/023.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/023.gif"},
{"id":1,"name":"Bulbasaur","speed":45,"special_defense":65,"special_attack":65,"defense":49,"attack":49,"hp":45,"types":["poison","grass"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/001.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/001.gif"},
{"id":12,"name":"Butterfree","speed":70,"special_defense":80,"special_attack":90,"defense":50,"attack":45,"hp":60,"types":["flying","bug"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/012.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/012.gif"},
{"id":96,"name":"Drowzee","speed":42,"special_defense":90,"special_attack":43,"defense":45,"attack":48,"hp":60,"types":["psychic"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/096.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/096.gif"},
{"id":52,"name":"Meowth","speed":90,"special_defense":40,"special_attack":40,"defense":35,"attack":45,"hp":40,"types":["normal"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/052.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/052.gif"},
{"id":27,"name":"Sandshrew","speed":40,"special_defense":30,"special_attack":20,"defense":85,"attack":75,"hp":50,"types":["ground"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/027.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/027.gif"},
{"id":147,"name":"Dratini","speed":50,"special_defense":50,"special_attack":50,"defense":45,"attack":64,"hp":41,"types":["dragon"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/147.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/147.gif"},
{"id":25,"name":"Pikachu","speed":90,"special_defense":50,"special_attack":50,"defense":40,"attack":55,"hp":35,"types":["electric"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/025.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/025.gif"},
{"id":4,"name":"Charmander","speed":65,"special_defense":50,"special_attack":60,"defense":43,"attack":52,"hp":39,"types":["fire"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/004.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/004.gif"},
{"id":16,"name":"Pidgey","speed":56,"special_defense":35,"special_attack":35,"defense":40,"attack":45,"hp":40,"types":["flying","normal"],"img_front":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_front/016.gif","img_back":"https://pldh.net/media/pokemon/gen5/blackwhite_animated_back/016.gif"}
]